Bazaar at Yomogi Nursery today!
Please come join us!
Could it be... Ioryogi?
Is there anyone else besides me with this form?
Obviously it's me!
Get your hand off of me!
R-Right!
Ko-ba-!
Ioryogi?
Ioryogi!
What?
Are you taking a nap in the middle of the road?
If you're sleepy, going home first and then sleeping on the futon would be a better—
I... I... I'm not napping!!
Kobato.
How do I do this again?
The simplest things in life
end up being the most difficult.
I just want to smile when I'm happy
and sing a song whenever I please.
I was told, "Someday,
your dream will come true."
But when exactly will that be?
I can't wait that long!
I spread my arms
on the count of one two three
and gather all the light in the world.
Tell me,
isn't there something I can do?
Even if someone hurts my feelings,
I'll keep running toward the light.
Even if I trip, fall, and cry my eyes out, I still believe.
Although it may seem silly...
I believe in tomorrow.
Production
The Kobato Protection Group
...Mysterious Lifeform, Part 2.
Ioryogi, what happened to you?
Don't "what happened" me! You can't tell just by looking at me?
Well...
Um....
Ioryogi, you're somewhat muddy!
Get a clue!
Anyway, just listen up!
It's rather bleak out today, huh.
It's okay.
Huh?
I'm sure it'll clear up.
That'd be nice.
Ioryogi?
I'll bring something that'll sell really well.
Thank you so much!
So I said.
But I'm not going to bring anything!
I've been fed up with pretending to be a
stuffed animal around that Nursery for so long.
Maybe I'll go to that bear's place and eat a ton of baumkuchen...
It's still in the strangest place.
One Mont Blanc!
Got it!
Cut it into fours, please!
Bear's Baumkuchen Shop
Happy Hour
Right Now
Is mine ready yet?
One baumkuchen, please.
The customer who ordered three slices?
Sorry for the wait!
Is mine done yet?
Please wait just a moment. It's coming right up!
Here are six slices!
How much longer for the long one?
Wait just a sec... two minutes left!
Doing well, aren't you?
Yeah. It actually was Zuisho's idea.
You've become quite important, huh.
Next time, let's increase the
varieties! We can have chocolate, etc.
Not a bad idea.
Let's do it, little by little!
You guys have really gotten used to this, huh.
In the beginning, we were worried about how things would turn out,
but we somehow managed to catch a good wave.
You no longer get my sarcasm either.
Huh?
Nothing, nothing.
Oh, and we've also started a home delivery service!
Here.
Oh, from the Bear's Baumkuchen Shop?
I've been waiting for this.
Thanks, as always.
Doesn't matter.
It's not the usual bird guy this time. Are you a new worker?
No.
Ah, so part-time help then?
There was a time when I had three part-time jobs myself.
I was abused terribly by a selfish shopkeeper.
Is that all you have to say? Then goodbye.
Oh, actually—
I've also been to this labyrinth like place.
It was another really weird location, with a ton of strange rooms...
We're on break right now
Looking at how well you guys fit into your roles now,
I've completely forgotten what you guys even used to look like in the past.
This body isn't all bad.
Being hairy is kinda, uh... But otherwise, if we're just careful, things will work out!
Getting used to something is scary, isn't it?
Like I feel like I've always been in this form ever since I was born!
Honestly...
I can't believe that happened... It all feels like a dream.
More like a nightmare for us.
It really feels like it's been a long time since then, doesn't it?
I guess it does.
It we look at it logically, we
really had no chance of winning.
The enemy was too terrible.
It was almost like a one-sided beatdown.
We fell apart pretty fast too, didn't we?
I feel like I stepped on someone back then...
I wonder who it could've been?
It was me.
What?!
It was you, Master Genko? I-I'm so sorry!
It's all in the past.
Besides, it's not like we had the time to get angry over every little thing like that back then.
I don't want to hear anything from you now, no matter how much you disagree.
And anyway, a law is a law.
Right now, there's nothing else for us to do but bake baumkuchen
and wait for things to come to a close.
Right?
We were so close then!
We weren't!
Now is a time for repentance!
You can't be thinking or saying terrible things like, "Oh, we were so close"!
Exactly!
Next time we step foot in the heavenly world,
we won't get away with just being turned into a bear and a bird!
Surely I'll be turned into a teddy bear,
and this guy won't even be turned into a bird; just bird bait.
T-That's terrible! You're the only one who gets to be something cute?! No fair!
Well anyway, absolutely do not, on any account, start any trouble!
You got it?
W-What?
Don't eat that!
That's important merchandise!
That stingy bear didn't give me
more than one present in the end
Let's see now... eating sweet things makes you want to follow up with something salty, huh.
And then after eating something salty, I'll eat some more of this baumkuchen...
I wonder where I could get some salty food...
Soy sauce flavored would be nice, but I'm really craving salt...
Hmm... it gives me that unique sensation in my stomach.
What are you doing?
Sorry, I totally missed!
Woah, the ball came back!
That's weird...
Whatever, come on!
Damn kids! All of them...
What's so fun about playing with a ball?
Woah, what the—!
What exactly is going—
Hey, stop it!
I'm not edible!
Oh no you don't. This is my dessert. There's no way you're getting this baumkuchen!
If you don't cut it out, I'll burn you on a stake...!
Hey, cut it out!
Hey! Hey!
Damn you! Even if — I die — I won't — hand this box over!
Oh no, water's dangerous.
Another crappy situation.
I feel like I'm going to emit
something other than flames.
Body's so heavy...
This just went from bad to worse.
Smile
Coin Laundry
If I use that, I'll be dry in one go!
Dryers are stronger than I thought they would be...
Where am I?
Asahi Eatery
Is that so?
Really, that vegetable shop-
But I'm starving.
No, no, no, I can't. This is to slowly savor later.
I'm not a kid who can't... control himself...
No, no, no!
This delicious smell is—!
What is that mysterious thing?
Welcome to Mokona Land!
To all of the little ladies and gentleman!
Don't have so much fun that you end up getting lost!
With that being said, crank up the enjoyment meter to max!
I've gotten lost in some strange place.
Oh, that's right! That delicious smell...
Famous Oden
Wow, everything looks delicious!
Ow...
Oh no!
I apologize!
Hey, wait a second!
I'm so sorry!
Dang it...
I might look like a stuffed animal, but I'm not actually a stuffed animal...
I need to hurry up and escape or else
someone might take my box of baumkuchen!
Huh? Where is this?
What's he doing?
I'll get you whichever one you like.
Don't tell me this is...
Papa, get that one!
All right, here we go..
T-This is...
Yay!
Hit the Target?!
Isn't it nice?
Papa, I want that blue doggie.
That one, right?
You mean me?!
Almost but not quite!
Oh, I missed?
This is no laughing matter!
This time I'll definitely...
Uh oh... it's on a collision course!
You missed again!
So close!
That's strange...  All right, next time I'll definitely—!
Huh? Did it just move?
It didn't move! Papa's just not very good at this.
Dang it... at this rate, I'm just
gonna get more and more fired up!
Good luck, Papa!
Here we go... I'll definitely get it this time!
Let's see how things go this time!
Gah, a good adult shouldn't get fired up over this! He should just give up!
Close!
I'll try too!
We'll help out too!
What?!
We just can't seem to hit it, can we?
Leave it to me.
Don't let my appearance fool you.
I was once feared as the legendary
Ms. Bullet of the Hit the Target game.
Who the heck are you?!
Uh oh, it doesn't count if it doesn't fall over!
Huh? What did you say?
All right then. Everybody,
let's combine our strength!
No, don't!
That blue one still hasn't fallen.
As if I could stand being some kid's plaything.
I did it!
Hit the Target
Congratulations!
Huh? It's not here. I can't find it!
Huh? It fell just now, didn't it?
Yeah, it definitely did! Everyone saw it, right?
Man, what a terrible day.
At least I've come this far—
And so that's what happened.
And you, your posters got torn down so you've been running around till now?
Because no one came to the bazaar.
Well, it really was such a small scale thing.
Whether the posters had been torn down or not,
it was foolhardy to expect so much
from a Nursery bazaar to begin with.
If things were going to turn out like this,
perhaps it would've been better if I
had never suggested we do a bazaar.
No, that's not true.
What's important is going through with your actions once you've decided upon them.
Even if you face difficulties, you can't give up.
Right.
Even if you get drenched in water or hit by a sniper.
Huh?
No, it's nothing.
It's action that's the important thing.
Just because there aren't customers doesn't mean you should get so downhearted.
Welcome!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Welcome back, Kobato!
You're late!
Look it! We've sold this much!
The weather fortune dolls sold too!
Thanks to you, Kobato, I managed to find an unimaginable treasure.
How long are you gonna
stand there spaced out for?
U-Uh, I'm sorry!
With this many customers, there aren't enough helping hands.
So you hurry up and help out too.
Yes!
Kobato.
Thank you so much.
It's because of your hard work that we managed to get so many people.
No! I didn't—!
Look.
Everyone's... having a good time.
And it's all thanks to you.
Kobato.
Domoto!
Thank you for going out of your way to come here!
You're quite welcome.
I had a lot of fun and got a lot of stuff.
I'm so glad!
But you know, I really wanted to get
something directly from you before I leave.
Oh, that's right! I made a stand too!
I wonder what happened to it...
1 for 500 Yen
None of them have sold...
Well, of course not.
No one would want something like this mysterious sheepenguinchicken thing.
Well then, I'll buy one.
Really?
Yup.
Thank you!
It has a very individualistic feel to it. That's just like you, Kobato.
Hm... a bunny?
D-Domoto!
Today was a wonderful day!
Not for me!
Really?
Really! Did you not listen to my story?
Um... was it really?
Don't "was it really" me!
But I managed to protect the most important thing, so I guess things turned out okay.
Once I get back, I'm gonna devour that thing!
No, I'm going to savor the taste and feast on it!
It?
It.
It... what is it?
Huh? It's gone. My baumkuchen is gone!
No way, we're going back to the Nursery to get it.
Oh, you're talking about your
baumkuchen? It was sold off very quickly.
What the hell did you do?!
You said so yourself, Ioryogi. "'I'll bring something that'll sell really well."
That something was the baumkuchen, wasn't it?
Thank you so much!
Today's score is...
80 points for your passion about the bazaar, but...
Since I'm disappointed, you get a total of minus 300 points!
What??
How come, Ioryogi? Are you disappointed because of me? If so, I apologize!!
It's not something you can fix by apologizing!
Then I'll give you one of the cute
bunnies I made, so please cheer—
As if I need that!!
T-Then as a bonus, I'll add one more for you!
I said I don't need that thing!!
Then I'll add a cute bear and sheep as well!
I can't tell one from the other! They all look like mystery lifeforms to me!
That's so mean, Ioryogi!
Even though we all want to fly,
we're being deceived by gravity.
In reality, everybody can already fly.
The reason why that child looks so sad
might be because she left her shadow somewhere.
If so...
If telling you "Thank you",
or hearing "Thank you" just makes you smile,
then doing those things will make me happy.
And they'll make you happy too.
Don't worry, we're together.
It's mysterious as to why tears roll down
even though I'm happy.
Next
...Warmth of a Chilling Wind.